<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KeyControl on @PSUStevens Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/tags/keycontrol/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KeyControl on @PSUStevens Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 08:08:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.psustevens.com/tags/keycontrol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Another KeyControl Security Admin From Active Directory</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/10/08/2021-10-08-how-to-add-another-security-admin-from-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 08:08:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/10/08/2021-10-08-how-to-add-another-security-admin-from-ad/</guid>
      <description>To get started here is what you will need to complete the steps in this post:
 A deployed Entrust KeyControl v5.4 cluster connected to Active Directory (Click this sentence to learn how to do this) Active Directory account info to be added  Now, let&amp;rsquo;s get started&amp;hellip;
Add a Second KeyControl Security Administrator from Active Directory   Click Security from the menu bar then click the blue Actions button and select Create User</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Connect KeyControl 5.4 to Active Directory</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/10/05/2021-10-05-how-to-connect-keycontrol-5.4-to-activedirectory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 08:08:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/10/05/2021-10-05-how-to-connect-keycontrol-5.4-to-activedirectory/</guid>
      <description>To get started here is what you will need to complete the steps in this post:
 A deployed Entrust KeyControl v5.4 cluster (Click this sentence to learn how to do this) Active Directory service account  Now, let&amp;rsquo;s get started&amp;hellip;
Connect KeyControl to Active Directory   Log in to the deployed Entrust KeyControl cluster. Once logged in:
 Click the Settings menu item Under the &amp;ldquo;General Settings&amp;rdquo; group click Authentication   Settings &amp;gt; Authentication     Click the Type drop-down box and select LDAP from the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deploy Entrust KeyControl 5.4</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/10/01/how-to-deploy-entrust-keycontrol-5.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:45:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/10/01/how-to-deploy-entrust-keycontrol-5.4/</guid>
      <description>Around this time last year I wrote about how to deploy a 2-node HyTrust KeyControl cluster. That post covered KeyControl version 5.2.1. You can find that blog post over here.
This post is very similar. The difference between it and the last post is that I will cover Entrust KeyControl version 5.4.. Are you scratching your head about the name change? Head over to this post I wrote about changes that occurred in January of this year where I talk about HyTrust being acquired by Entrust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deploy a HyTrust KeyControl v5.2.1, 2-Node Cluster</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/31/how-to-deploy-a-hytrust-keycontrol-2-node-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 14:04:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/31/how-to-deploy-a-hytrust-keycontrol-2-node-cluster/</guid>
      <description>To get started here is what you will need to complete the steps in this post:
 KeyControl OVA v5.2.1 vCenter and ESX host at least version 6.5 or greater 2 vCPU, 8GB RAM, 60GB disk per KeyControl node Network address information such as:  IP address (one per node) Subnet mask Gateway address DNS server information DNS registered hostname for each node    Deploy the First HyTrust KeyControl Appliance  Log in to the Virtual Center Appliance (VCSA).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
