<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on @PSUStevens Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on @PSUStevens Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 05:41:14 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.psustevens.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I DIY&#39;d My Career Into a Sales Engineer</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/29/how-i-diyd-my-career-into-a-sales-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 05:41:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/29/how-i-diyd-my-career-into-a-sales-engineer/</guid>
      <description>This post is one of those times where I put tech aside. So, if you are only interested in tech-related blog posts, then you may want to skip this one. If I caught your interest (W00t!!), then please continue.
 &amp;ldquo;MacGyvering&amp;rdquo; My Career Path My career path didn&amp;rsquo;t follow a traditional plan or approach. But, then again, does that really happen to anyone? If you can say yes, then good for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Blog With Hugo - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/26/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 12:21:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/26/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part5/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I last updated this series. I apologize to anyone who is following it and lost interest. I hope to be quicker in future series I write.
 Introduction In this post, I will walk through what I do to publish my blog to Github. I use private and public repositories and GitHub Desktop. This way, I can do some testing in my private repo before pushing it to my public repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogtober Tech Edition 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/24/blogtober-tech-edition-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 01:34:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/24/blogtober-tech-edition-2020/</guid>
      <description>I hit my first anniversary of blogging this past September. As you may have noticed, I&amp;rsquo;ve been a bit lax over the main course of this year. I know, I know. With the whole COVID thing going on this year, you would have thought there would have been more time to blog. After sheltering in place and being forced to work from home, I got busier. At the height of the pandemic, I was on six or more conference calls a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Blog With Hugo - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/12/20/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 01:24:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/12/20/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part4/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post, I covered how to customize the theme for your Hugo site. I apologize if it was a bit long. This post is considerably shorter. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk through how to configure Google Analytics for your site. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
 Before we get started&amp;hellip; If you are already familiar with Google Analytics, then this will be a short read for you. All you need to do is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Blog With Hugo - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/12/18/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 01:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/12/18/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part3/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post, I covered how to build your first Hugo site using the Hugo Future Imperfect Slim theme. I also walked through the process to create the first blog post for your new site. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk through different customization options for the theme. The customizations aren&amp;rsquo;t exhaustive but are good enough for you to get started and possibly expand on. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First International VMUG</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/11/06/my-first-international-vmug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 01:20:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/11/06/my-first-international-vmug/</guid>
      <description>This week I am attending my very first VMworld Europe in, of all places, beautiful, Barcelona, Spain. I&amp;rsquo;ll write a synopsis of VMworld after it&amp;rsquo;s over, and I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to my blogging series after VMworld is over. For this post, I want to cover my first very International VMUG event. Continue reading for my viewpoint of the event.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t find out about the VMUG until the very last minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Blog With Hugo - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/11/01/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 13:07:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/11/01/building-a-blog-with-hugo-part2/</guid>
      <description>In the first part of this series, I wrote about why I chose to use Hugo to develop this blog and GitHub Pages to host it. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk through the steps to create a Hugo site, apply a theme, and create a very simple blog post. So, let&amp;rsquo;s get going!
 Before You Get Started Before you get started, you need to gather a few bits and bytes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Blog With Hugo</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/10/11/building-a-blog-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 16:02:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/10/11/building-a-blog-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>If you read my very first post, you would know that I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about writing a blog for years. I&amp;rsquo;ve been blogging for years for employers. But, just recently, I finally launched my first technical blog. The one you are reading right now. I also have a travel blog that only gets updated when I travel for vacation. In this blog series, I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about how I built my blog site using Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing... Me</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/09/30/introducing-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 08:48:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/09/30/introducing-me/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first post of my technical blog where I will write about virtualization technologies such as VMware and Microsoft, desktop and server technologies from Microsoft and the occasional script based on PowerShell.
 A bit about me I hail from Pittsburgh, PA, but now live in New Hampshire. My wife and I have lived in New England for many years. We moved up here so I could work for Dell as a technical marketing engineer in their storage group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
