<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Improvement on @PSUStevens Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/tags/self-improvement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Improvement on @PSUStevens Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 David Stevens</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 16:19:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.psustevens.com/tags/self-improvement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Quick Fork in the Job Road</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2023/12/12/a-quick-fork-in-the-job-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 16:19:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2023/12/12/a-quick-fork-in-the-job-road/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s put it this way.  I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking for a new job.  But due to an unforeseen curveball, I now work for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.purestorage.com/&#34;&gt;Pure Storage&lt;/a&gt;.  This wasn&amp;rsquo;t a planned move, but looking back (6 months now).  I have no complaints!!  I wish all of my friends and colleagues at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.entrust.com/&#34;&gt;Entrust&lt;/a&gt; the best of luck and I know we will see each other at future trade shows or somewhere else along our travels.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Changes!</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/02/14/new-year-new-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 11:45:19 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2021/02/14/new-year-new-changes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most people post their New Years&amp;rsquo; blog posts within the first week of the new year.  But, there have been some things brewing that I needed to wait to complete.  This blog post isn&amp;rsquo;t like my other posts.  It&amp;rsquo;s a brief look back at what transpired in 2020 and what I hope to accomplish this year. I also have an announcement about some exciting new changes that have been brewing since late last year.  Before I forget, Happy New Year!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I DIY&#39;d My Career Into a Sales Engineer</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/29/how-i-diyd-my-career-into-a-sales-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 05:41:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2020/10/29/how-i-diyd-my-career-into-a-sales-engineer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This post is one of those times where I put tech aside.  So, if you are only interested in tech-related blog posts, then you may want to skip this one.  If I caught your interest (W00t!!), then please continue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;macgyvering-my-career-path&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;MacGyvering&amp;rdquo; My Career Path&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My career path didn&amp;rsquo;t follow a traditional plan or approach.  But, then again, does that really happen to anyone?  If you can say yes, then good for you.  When I was growing up, I always wanted to be a garbage man.  Yes, I know that isn&amp;rsquo;t politically correct today, but this is my blog.  At one point, I also considered being a fireman.  I think, as a little boy, many of us had these grandiose plans.  Oh, to be seven years old again!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing... Me</title>
      <link>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/09/30/introducing-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 08:48:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.psustevens.com/2019/09/30/introducing-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first post of my technical blog where I will write about virtualization technologies such as VMware and Microsoft, desktop and server technologies from Microsoft and the occasional script based on PowerShell.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-bit-about-me&#34;&gt;A bit about me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I hail from Pittsburgh, PA, but now live in New Hampshire.  My wife and I have lived in New England for many years.  We moved up here so I could work for Dell as a technical marketing engineer in their storage group.   I supported the EqualLogic and Compellent SAN products and their NAS front-end for both of those systems by the name of Fluid File System.  After a few years, I moved to a startup by the  name of DataGravity where I was also a technical marketing engineer.  After a few years at DataGravity, HyTrust came along and scooped us up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
